# BRITTANY E. WEBB

# BRITTANYWEBBE@GMAIL.COM WEB/.NET DEVELOPER 937.902.9159 DAYTON OH WEB/.NET DEVELOPER

#### **ABOUT ME**

Almost 5 years experience as a .NET application developer. Graduated with a B.S. in Computer Information Systems and currently expanding my web specific development skill set as an apprentice at Sparkbox. I have experience in front-end development, back-end/server-side development, UI/UX design, ORACLE database, as well as system conversion and pre/post-production maintenance.

#### **OUALITIES**

- Expertise in debugging, troubleshooting, and fixing existing code.
- Excellent problem solving skills.
- Inventive and creative solutions.
- Self driven, motivated individual.
- Team player, who is not afraid to take leadership role.

#### **EDUCATION**

**Urbana University - Bachelors of Science in Computer Information Systems** 

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Apprenticeship [January 2016 - Present] Sparkbox - Dayton, OH

Learning web standards and mac/console development skills.

WEB SKILLS
HTML5
CSS3/SCSS (Media Queries)
Handlebars

APP SKILLS RUBY RUBY ON RAILS TOOLS
Mac - Command Line, Atom
Adobe - Illustrator, PhotoShop
GIT/GITHUB
RSPEC

### Software Developer [March 2014 - July 2015] Ohio Secretary of State - Columbus, OH

- Supported a suite of internal ASP.NET 4.5 C# MVC Web based applications. This
  includes fixing reported bugs and coding new functionality in all tiers of
  application, utilizing Kendo UI toolkit, JavaScript, HTML/CSS, C#, Linq, SQL on a
  daily basis.
- Created front-end of SPA .Net application utilizing Knockout Js and Bootstrap.
   Helped design JSON return object from API calls my front-end consumed.

WEB SKILLS	APP SKILLS	TOOLS
HTML5	<b>ASP.NET MVC Framework</b>	<b>Windows - Visual Studio, Office</b>
CSS3 (Media Queries)	C#	PL/SQL Developer
JAVASCRIPT / JQuery	LINQ	
KNOCKOUT JS(MVVM Pattern)	SQL (Oracle DB)	
Bootstrap JS		
<b>SOAP and RESTful Web Services</b>		

## Software Developer [March 2009 - Aug 2012] Tyler Technologies - Dayton, OH

- Responsible for testing and fixing bugs in Web Application.
- Designed and developed modifications to Web Application, delivering functionality detailed in the technical specifications. Often worked on all tiers of Web Application to implement new functionality.
- Worked with and created Web Services to retrieve data from database.
- Developed client side validation code using JavaScript.
- Developed database side validation code using SQL.
- Involved in Application UI redesign. Met with outside consultant to help create new design. Implemented finalized design using HTML and CSS. This process also involved updating code to meet standards that would make Web Application cross browser compatible.

WEB SKILLS	APP SKILLS	TOOLS
HTML5	ASP.NET C#	<b>Windows - Visual Studio, Office</b>
C223	SQL (Oracle DB)	JIRA
JAVASCRIPT / JQuery		PL/SQL Developer
XML/XSL		
<b>SOAP and RESTful Web Services</b>		